Preliminary Inventory to the Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers WAG.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Interview and AFSCME Local Files, 1948-1984.
  - Locals: General, 1957-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - General: Leaflets, Newsletters, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Maritime Port Council, 1961-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Membership By Locals, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10a)
  - Local 154, NYC Employees, 1957-1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local 237, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Local 237, Teamsters v. Local 1783, Housing Authority, 1957-1964 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Local 299, Recreational Employees, 1957-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Local 371, Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Local 371, SSEU, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Local 371, SSEU, 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Local 371, SSEU Strike, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1968-1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Local 372, Board of Education, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Local 372, School Lunch Aides, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Local 374, NY/Brooklyn Botanical Garden, 1957-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Local 376, Parks Department, 1967-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Local 384, CUNY, 1957-1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Local 442, Subway Supervisors, 1961-1964 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local 824, Laborers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local 924-376, Laborers, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local 983, Motor Vehicle Operator's Strike, 1956-1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Local 1070, Judicial Conference, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Local 1087, Bureau of Community Education, Prevailing Rate, 1956-1965 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Local 1113, Finance Employees, 1958-1966 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Local 1306, Museum of Natural History, 1956-1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Local 1321-1482, Queensborough Public Library, 1966-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Local 1320, Public Works, 1957-1963 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Local 1396, Triborough Bridge and Tunnel, Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Local 1407, Accountants, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Local 1501, New York Zoo, 1956-1961 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Local 1503, Metropolitan Museum, 1959-1974 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Local 1549, CWA Raid, 1965-1974 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Local 1597, Custodial Employees, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Series VI: Chapter Drafts.
  - Chapter Headings, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Early Years, to 1950, Chapter 1, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - We Have Faith in You, Chapter 2, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Who Built This Union, Robert Moses, Chapter 3, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining, Not Collective Begging, Chapter 4, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Never Again in Awe of Power, Chapter 5, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - You Can Fight City Hall, Chapter 7, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hospital Elections, Chapter 8, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Collective Bargaining: Seat of Power, Chapter 9, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gotbaum Takes Command, Chapter 10, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Inside Union Bureaucracy, Chapter 11, draft, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Political Machine…Union Made, Chapter 12, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Operation Price Watch, former Chapter 12, draft, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Political Participation, Chapter 13, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Learn, Baby Learn…, Chapter 14, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Expanding Union Services, Chapter 15, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - In the Shadow of the Crisis, Chapter 16, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - The Fiscal Crisis - Threat and Response, Chapter 17, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Contest of Power, Chapter 18, drafts, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Series VII: Unprocessed Files, 1940s-2000.
  - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA), 1980s (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - ADA National Board, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ADA Nassau County, Roskoff and Leon Shull Meeting, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Grass Roots Insurgency - Wurf v. Zander (1964), 1980s (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Shier, Carl, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pollard Case, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Students, 1979-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Summer Lease, Kaufman-Morgenstein, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Universal Utilities, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Warschauer Society: Jack Weinstein, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bush Administration: 1 Year Review, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Credit Charges Summary, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Credit Charges (World Pass), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dershowitz/American Jewish Congress, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - IRA (PSC/CUNY and Chemical), 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - IRA Transfer, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - ADA New York City, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ADA National Board, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ADA Nassau County, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ADA State Board, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ADA New York, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ADA Open Letter: Alan Roskoff, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ADA Long Island Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ADA Long Island Membership, 1986-1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ADA long Island Activities, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - ADA Long Island Bank Balances and Dues, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - ADA Long Island Activities, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ADA: Alan Roskoff, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence: Isaccs, Amy, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - ADA Convention: Israeli Resolution, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cimitile, Carole, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - ADA, NYS and Long Island Checking Account, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - ADA; Homeless Housing, Long Island, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: ADA, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - ADA Long Island, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - ADA NYS May Meeting, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Mailing Zip Codes, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Long Island Organizations, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - McTiernan, Jack: Syracuse, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Mittermeyer, Paul: Rochester, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence: ADA National Office, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - ADA NYS, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - ADA NYS Billings, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - ADA NYS Lobbyist, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - ADA NYS Mailings, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Sheffer, Ethel, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - ADA: Ethel Sheffer Report, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - ADA Summer Correspondence, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Bowest Corporation (Mortgage), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - American Jewish Committee: Task Force on Pluralism, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Olicker, Ethel, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - ADA National Exec. Committee: Kosovo Resolutions, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Liu, Liming (Insurance), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Luba, Sy (a/c), Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - New York Labor History Association (NYLHA), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - NYLHA: February 23, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - NYLHA: January 13, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - NYLHA Minutes and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - NYLHA Conference, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - ADA: NGO Representative, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - NYLHA: October 7, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - NYLHA: Annual Meeting, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Presidential Pardon: Stanley Feingold and Joe Galu, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - PSC/CUNY Savings Account, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence: Press, Dan, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - ADA National Convention, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - ADA Convention: Bosnia Resolution, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - ADA: Schumer Meeting Names and Addresses, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - DC 37 Interview, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - ADA Long island Exec. Comm.: Voting Inequalities, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - VanHees, Mindy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - lowey, Nita, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Letter Re: Exec Comm. Action on Kosovo, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - ADA Long Island: Resolution on Kosovo, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - ADA Paid-up Members: 1st Quarter, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - ADA Nominations Comm., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - ADA Long Island Exec. Comm.: February, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - ADA Long Island Exec. Comm.: October, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - ADA National, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - ADA long Island, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - ADA Long Island Elections, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Elder Hostel: Honduras, Guatemala, Belize, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Iraq-U.S., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Peace in Stages: Israel, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Israel: Contemporary Developments, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Jackson, Jesse, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Fitness Club: Great Neck, Undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - ADA Long Island, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ADA Long Island Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Socialist International Meetings, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dartmouth Review Incident, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - American Jewish Comm. (LI): Bd. of Governors, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - AJC (LI): Gary Sazer, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dike, Rad, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Socialists of America, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Adelman, Nora, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - FDR-Humphrey Dinner, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Humphrey-FDR Dinner, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - International Resolutions, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - ADA Long Island Leaflet, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - ADA Long Island: Congressman, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - ADA NYS Lobbying Day: Albany, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ADA National Office Directives, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Bonds: Tripp and Co., 1991 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: January-April, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Forward (Jewish), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Fundamentalists Anonymous, 1990s (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Government Activism, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Bush Admin.: Kamber Group and Civil Rights, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Selby, Stella, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - TIAA, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - US Army: Medals, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Gotbaum, Vic, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Girard, Harlan (Non-Lethal Weapons), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - BB to Vic Gotbaum: International Correspondence, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Gotbaum, Betsy, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Kramer, Gail, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Lefkowitz, Hugh, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Levine, Bob (USSR), 1991 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Levine, Mickey: Memoirs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Levine, Mickey, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Levine, Mickey: Memorial, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Long island Progressive Coalition: Social Justice Comm., 1998 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Prescriptions, Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - United Nations: WVF, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - WVF, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - ADA Long Island, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - American Jewish Comm., 1999 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Bosnia, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Epstein, Bill: Luncheon, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Netherlands Discount Tickets, Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Israel, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Luba, Sy (a/c), Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - New Jersey Statute on Gypsies, etc., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - NYLHA: January, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - North Shore Hospital, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - NYLHA: Fall, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - NYLHA: Constitution, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - NYLHA: Brenda Zwiekel, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence: November-February, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence; June-October, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence: March-May, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Israel: Speech, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Speech: Israel Visit - Hamas Fundamentalists, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Speech: Peace Now in Israel, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: June-June, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Hemg, Sue, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hanover, New Hampshire, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hanover, New Hampshire, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Freidel, Frank, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Karmi, Nachman and Sara, 1960s-1970s (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Israel-Arabs, 1947-1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - University of Utrecht (Papers), 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jan 2000-Feb 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sepersky, Letter to, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Feb 1997-May 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1997-Nov 1997 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1998-Mar 1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Seperky, Letter to, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - NYS-ADA Constitution, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - ADA Coordinating Council-History, Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Legislators Addresses, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - ADA Testimonial Remarks, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - ADA Westchester, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - ADA: Albany, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Apr 1995-Dec 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - NYS-ADA Dispute, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Jillson, Irene, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Berger, Henry: Regulation Letter to, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Schneier, Ned: NYS-ADA, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rich, Evelyn, 1989-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, May 1983-Nov 1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (Friends), 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education License to Teach, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Housing: Public/American Veterans Comm., 1940s (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1983-May 1984 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Winnant, John (Europe), 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - European Trip, Jul 1951 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.: Dissertation on, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Wells, John, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Wellesley Summer Institution, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cooper Union Address, Dec 1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Cooper Union: Course Notes, 1952-1953 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Academic Freedom Comm. (AFC): 50th Anniversary, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Winant, John, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - College Records, 1941-1950 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - CUNY Promotion, 1955-1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1992-Dec 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Winant, 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (Personal), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Stark, Irwin, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - AFC: American Civil Liberties Union, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Stark, Orwin (Dorson, Norman), 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Menand, Louis, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - ILGWU, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Politics, 1949-1952 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Saxe, Emmanuel, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Teachers College, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Winant Research Project, 1950-1953 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (Winant Project), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence (Winant Project), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (Winant Project), 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Annunziata, Frank, 1974-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Asher, Bob, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Blaesser, Willard, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Black and Puerto Rican Student Community: CUNY, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University, 1946-1951 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Gotbaum, Vic, 1978-1985 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Great Neck Estates: 75th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Harrington, Death of, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Hendel Memorial Convocation, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Union Power and New York, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Forward: 90th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Radicalism, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Union Power and NY Contract, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Union Power and NY Reviews, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Jan 1999-Mar 1999 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1998-Sep 1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Sep 1998-Dec 1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - American Veterans Committee, 1977-1985 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Jul 1992-Sep 1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Nov 1997-Dec 1997 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Jun 1997-Aug 1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - ADA: 50th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - USSR History, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Mar 1998-May 1998 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Dec 1998- Jan 1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence (Israel), Jan 1983-Apr 1983 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Feingold, Stan, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Forward Association, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Forward Articles, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Forverts (Forward: Jewish and Russian), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Freedman, Monroe, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Goodrich, Michael, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Great Neck Home (Bady, Jerry), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Great Neck Senior Center, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gubic, Marijan, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hill, Felicity, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - They Were Not Silent: The Jewish Labor Movement and the Holocaust, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hospital Mergers, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights, Declaration of, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Israel, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Israel: Analysis, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Israel: Clippings, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Israel, Steve/Seltzer, Regina (Democrats for Congress), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Israel: General, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Israel: General, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Israel: Tour, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Friedman, Tom, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Jewish Population Movement (Article), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Israel: Soviet Aliyah, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - One Year After the Assassination: Where Are We?, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Israel: Where is It Heading?, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Israel: Civil Rights, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Yiftah, Kibbutz, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Conference of Non-Governmental Organizations (CONGO): Board Meeting, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - ADA, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Retirement: Kendal on Hudson, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - United Nations, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - NGO Fundraising, 1997-2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Lyon's Article (France), 2001 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Jewish Immigrant Experience, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Letter from London, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Liberalism is Alive and Well (Article), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Long Island Railroad (Cell Phone Usage), 1999 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - McGure, Ron, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - McCarthy, Thaddeus, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Dr. McKinley, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Menon, Bhaskar, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Nathan, Clarence (Hankin), 2000 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - North Shore Glass Co., Undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Nyack Hospital, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - NYC Walks, 1979-1995 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Photographs (Lawmakers), Undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - NYC Politics and Immigrants (Clippings), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - University of Vermont, Lecture at, Apr 1999 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Benjamin Duarte: Painter-Carpenter-Roofing, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Petaluma Jewish Community, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - PSC/CUNY Federal Credit Union, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, Feb 2001 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, Mar 2001 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, Apr 2001 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - NGO Committee on Disarmament: Publication Committee, May 2001 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Randolph A. Phillip, 1979-2001 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Rhone River, Paris, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - All Weather Guard Roofing, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Ross, Norman and family, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Scopes Trial: 70 Years Later, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Scopes Trial: 70 Years Later (Clippings), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Social Security, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Dr. Steven Spencer, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Stoler, Mark, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Tax Speech II, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Norman Thomas High School, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Tyler, Gus, 1991-2001 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Triangle Fire, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Jewish Cemetery (Venice, Italy), 2000 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Candlelight Vigil: Assassinations of Shepard, Matthew and D. Barnett Slepian, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Freedman, James (Winant), 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Women in War by Willenz, June, Undated (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Workmen's Circle: Social and Economic Justice Committee, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - World Veterans Federation, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence, Oct 2007-Jan 2001 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Aug 2000-Oct 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Heritage), 1933-1954 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - TVA The New Deal, 1935-1945 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Transcendentalists, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Carter Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - American Labor Party and Henry Wallace, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, 1973-1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Browder, Earl, 1935-1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - CUNY: Radical Movements, 1929-1935, 1965-1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Old Left: War Our Heritage, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Baldwin, Bettie, 1935 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. as Governor, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - "What's Left? And Where Do We Go From Here?, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Old/New Left Views of the Roosevelt Presidency, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello (Mayor), 1966 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Tonkin Gulf Crisis, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Truman, Harry S. and Joe McCarthy, 1947-1967 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Failure Socialism in the U.S., 1951-1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Old/New Left (Education), Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Truman, Harry S. and McCarthyism, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Progressive Radical Forces, 1948-1952 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Laidler, Harry and the New Deal, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Southern Tenant Farmers (New Deal and N. Thomas), 1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - FDR and Politics of Protest: Progressivism, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Spanish Civil War, 1936-1939 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Holocaust, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - New Deal (Background and Europe), Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Blacks and Communism, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Popular Front Era: Revisionists, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Kristol-Zinn Articles, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Socialist Party U.S.A., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 32)